{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Míngtiān" ,
      "answer": "明天"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yǒu",
      "answer": "有"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shíjiān" ,
      "answer": "时间"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shuō",
      "answer": "说"
    },
    {
      "question": "Biān",
      "answer": "遍"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dǎqiú",
      "answer": "打球"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dǎ",
      "answer": "打"
    },
    {
      "question": "qiú",
      "answer": "球"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bàoqiàn",
      "answer": "抱歉"
    },
    {
      "question": "Máng",
      "answer": "忙"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kǒngpà",
      "answer": "恐怕"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xíng",
      "answer": "行"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xièxiè",
      "answer": "谢谢"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nǐmen",
      "answer": "你们"
    }
  ]
}
